The reality is that nobody ever
complains about gravity.
>> [laughter]
>> You've never seen an old person walking
through the mall all bent over and went,
"Gravity, I hate gravity. Wouldn't be
for gravity, I wouldn't be all bent
over. Gravity sucks." Never see that.
Why not? Because you can't change
gravity. Everyone knows gravity just is,
so we don't complain about it. So,
anything you're complaining about you
have to have a reference point in your
mind of something better, better job,
better country, better president, better
whatever. And what happens then is when
we become aware that we have this better
option that we're not willing to risk
creating. So, therefore we complain
about it. And it lets off steam, it gets
people to go together, yeah, I know, my
wife's the same way, whatever it is, but
we don't get a better result. I always
say, imagine a situation where every
woman in the world dies except my wife.
Big thing comes down from outer space,
zaps the earth with some energy field,
my wife happens to be in a lead mine
that day, she's the only one who
survived. Would I come to work and
complain about my wife? No. Why not?
She's the only one. There is no option,
right? So, we wouldn't complain about
it. If you're complaining, my response
to that is, what would you prefer? What
would you have to do to create that?